“艳舞女郎”
拉斯维加斯342哩
Las Vegas 342
上车
Hop in, pard
去哪处？
Where you going?
拉斯维加斯
Vegas!
上车吧，今天你行运
Come on. This is your lucky day
愿意的话，坐近点
You can sit a little closer if you want
打错主意
Bad idea
不准胡来  知道
Chill,okay? l am chilled
有你解闷，真开心
l am glad you will be such good company
我不喜欢布禄的歌
l don't like Garth Brooks
我也不喜欢
Me, neither
有谁喜欢？
l don't know anyone who does
打算不断亮出刀子？
You keeping that open the whole trip?
你有名字吗？
You got a name?
我停下来，让你下车好了
Look, l'll just pull over and you can get out
我从肯州，老远驶来
l drove all the way from Kansas
不想好心没好报，被人当猪宰
l ain't in the mood to get pig-stuck for doing someone a favor!  Okay?
我就把车泊去路旁
So l will just pull over
满意了吧？
All right?
那么…你有名字吗？
So.. have you got a name?
我叫谢夫
l'm Jeff
娜美
Nomi
少有的名字
What kind of name is that?
我妈妈是意裔
My mom was ltalian
意大利人？
ltalian, huh?
你是黑手党的党徒？难怪有刀
You a Mafia girl? That's why you got your blade?
去赌城干什么？搏杀？
Why you going to Vegas? Going to win?
当舞蹈员
l'm going to dance
表演私人艳舞？
You going to be one of them private escort dancers?
对不起
l'm sorry. l'm sorry
拉斯维加斯：不夜天的赌城
KBlD. You never go to sleep in Vegas
赌城到了
There she is
你来过？
You been here before?
来过，叔叔是河畔酒店的接待员
Sure My uncle is a host at the Riviera
赌钱吗？
Do you gamble?
不赌，怎赢？
Got to gamble if you want to win
我会赢
l'm going to win
用你箱子内的钱做赌本嘛
Then use that Mafia money in your suitcase
箱子留在车内吧
Leave your stuff in the car
我去找叔叔，替你介绍工作
l'll talk to my uncle. See if he can get you a job
不惯有人对你好？
Ain't anyone ever been nice to you?
玩吃角子机吗？
Want to play a slot machine?
十元，赢的话，你我五五分账
Here's ten bucks lf you win, we split it up
不得中饱私囊，我找叔叔去
No holding out on me either l'll go see my uncle
稍后这里再见
l'll meet you back here
不得了！
Holy shit!
犀利！试试较大的赌注吗？
Look at you! You want to try some silver dollars?
输清光？想赚外快吗？
Lose all your money, honey? Want to make some more?
只消十五分钟就赚得到
lt won't take you any longer than fifteen minutes
迟早你都要出来做！
Sooner or later, you'll have to sell it!
妈的！
Fuck!
混帐！
Shit!
那杂种溜掉！
Fuck! The fucker left!
干什么？这是我的汽车！
What are you doing? That's my car!
我失去了行李！
l want my suitcase!
别碰我的汽车
Get off my car!
别理会我！
Leave me alone!
行李箱内有什么？
So, what was in your suitcase?
没值钱的，私人物件而已
Nothing. Just my stuff Everything l had
妈的！初到步就倒霉！
Fuck! l just got here!
欢迎光临赌城
Welcome to Vegas
这里有熟人吗？
You know anyone here?
家人的电话呢？
Got any family you can call?
我没有家人
l don't have any family
你从哪处来？
Where are you from?
东部  东部哪处？
Back east. Where back east?
东部各处！
Different places!
这样吧
Look
要暂时栖身，可到我家
You can stay with me if you need a place to crash
地方浅窄
lt's not much
找到工作才搬走
Until you get a job
你在打我主意？
Are you hitting on me?
你不是妓女吧？
You're not a hooker?
六星期后
6 Weeks Later
安德鲁另一金曲：“迎风而行”
Andrew Carver, another smash ''Walk lnto The Wind''
看！
Check it out!
好看
They're great
不俗吧？
Neat, huh?
不俗，跟我一起去吗？
They are neat You want to come with me?
我们的舞蹈团来了个新女主角
We have this new lead She's realy good
我够钟上班
l have to go to work
你还有三小时才够钟
Jerk, you don't have to be at work for 3 hours
怎打发？看电视、吃薯片？
What will you do, watch TV and eat chips?
薯片呢？
Where are the chips?
给你吃掉？
Did you eat them?
你吃掉！   没有
Yes, you did. You did! l didn't
你有！   停手！
You did, you did! Stop!
跟我去嘛，让大家欣赏你的指甲
Come on, Nomi You can show off your nails
羡慕一番
They'll all be jealous
会羡慕？
You think?
我穿什么好？
What can l wear?
穿我上星期造的裙子
Wear the dress l made last week
皱纹裙？
The fringe?
我把头发束起
l'll put my hair up!
没时间束发了
We don't have time for that
我保证会尽快
l'll hurry. l promise!
大家赶快！两分钟后出场！
Okay, you guys, let's go! We got two minutes!
脱外衣！
Robes off!
情形怎样？安妮，你没穿衣服
Ladies, how we doing? Annie, you're naked
死慕莉！
Fuck you. Molly!
什么事？  破裂了
What happened? lt ripped
快将补好
lt's almost done
这条绳修不好，我下面就会走光
Molly, they'll see a smiling snatch if you don't fix this G-string
我快来了，安妮
l'll be right there, Annie
她可能故意剪断，暴露下体
She wants to smile here snatch Bet she cut the string herself
茱莉，你真刻薄，修补好
You're terrible, Julie. Okay, done
什么味道？
What's that smell?
猴子吃大蒜后，登台表演
The monkey act He feeds them garlic
好难闻
lt stinks
你想我无下装登台？
You want me onstage without a G?
我正在修补，别催，行吗？
l'm fixing it, Annie! Give me a minute! Jesus!
谁想看她的下体？
Who'd want to see her snatch?
我就不想
l sure wouldn't
我们都知道  娜美！
We know that Nomi!
跟着来！
Come on!
列队！四个八拍后出场，去！
Line up! You got four counts of eight. Let's go!
把花放在那处
Just set them over there
赶快！
Move it!
慕莉，我的绳裤！
Molly, my G!
巴不得她摔下楼梯吧？
Don't you wish she'd fall down the stairs?
去大堂看表演
Go watch the showroom
我可以去？
Can l go up there?
还有两个八拍！干什么？快去！
You got two counts of eight! What are you doing? Let's go! Move your ass!
各位来宾…
Ladies and gentlemen
星尘隆重介绍：姬丝桃小姐
the Stardust proudly presents Miss Cristal Connors!
什么红星我们都请得起
We could have brought anyone into this show
丽黛积逊、苏珊森玛…
LaToya, Suzanne, you name it
我们选中姬丝桃
We wanted Cristal
赌城的魅力，集于她一身
Cristal Connors defines what Las Vegas is all about
光芒四射、美艳动人、十分性感
She's dazzling, exciting and she's very, very sexy
重临本城，开心吗？
Are you glad to be back?
对这节目有什么看法？
How do you feel about the show?
精心制作，我希望能够胜任
lt's the best show l've ever been in l hope l can do it justice
绝对胜任，我们万分欢迎你
You did, and you will We're thrilled to have you here
我深感荣幸
l'm thrilled to be here
祝贺她吧
You, too
可不可以拍张献花照片？
Can we have one of you handing Cristal the flowers?
沙克
Zack?
沙克！你去献花
Zack! You do it
那位是娱乐总监沙克
That's Zack Carey, the entertainment director
多风度翩翩
He's so smooth
请笑纳，姬小姐
Your bouquet, Miss Connors
拍照后收下，行吗？
Can l keep them?
采访完毕！十分感谢各位
Okay, that's it! Thank you very much for coming. Thanks
这边来
This way, Cristal
应该送玫瑰给我
They could have gotten me roses
她多出色，对吗？
She's great, isn't she?
不算差劲
She doesn't suck
姬丝桃找你
Molly! Cristal needs you
跟我来
Come with me
充当我的助手，来
You can be my assistant. Come on
姬小姐
Yes, Miss Connors?
叫我姬丝桃吧
Cristal, please. And you are? l'm sorry
我叫慕莉
Molly Abrams
胸围太紧，压扁我的乳房
This top is too tight My breasts are getting crushed
我替你放松
l can loosen it for you
这处放松点，别太松
To here, maybe. No, a little less
奶头要罩得稳，以免波涛汹涌
l want my nipples to press, not look like they're levitating
谢谢你，亲爱的
Thanks, darling
你今晚的演出很精彩，姬…小姐
You were really great tonight, Miss... Cristal
过奖
Thanks, darling
这些花是安德鲁送的？
Andrew Carver sent you these?
既然咭片上是这样写
lf that's what the card says
我喜欢安德鲁
l just love him
我朋友娜美，舞蹈艺员 是吗？
This is my friend Nomi. She's a dancer. ls she now?
很有天份
Yes, and she's really good
在哪里跳舞？
Where do you dance, darling?
在猎豹会所
At the Cheetah
我不知你本领多高、有什么本领
l don't know how good you are, or what it is you're good at...
但在猎豹的话，你肯定不是跳舞
but if it's at the Cheetah, it's no dancing, l know that
你知个屁！
You don't know shit!
对不起，姬小姐
l'm sorry, Miss Connors
叫我姬丝桃
''Cristal''
已吩咐过你
l told you
姬丝桃
Cristal
你朋友的指甲不错
Your friend has nice nails
她自己修甲
She does them herself
也许叫她替我修
Maybe she can do mine sometime
我在这里干活
l work here, okay?
不想惹她生气，打破饭碗
l need my paycheck l don't want her pissed at me
对不起
l'm sorry!
离谱
Jesus, Nomi
我载你上班
l'll drive you to work, okay?
不上班
l'm not going
不怕革职？
They'll fire you
无所谓
l don't care
有所谓  无所谓
Yes, you do. No, l don't
我们去吧
Let's go
去哪里？
Where?
还有哪里？
You know where
她跳得不错
She can dance, can't she?
她自以为不错
She thinks she can
我去跟她跳
l'm gonna go dance with her
上班时间跳舞？不怕老板？
You can't do that. You're working! T.C. will have your ass!
老板在河畔酒店赌骰子
T.C.'s at the Riviera, playing craps
想跳舞吗？  我在跳舞
Want to dance? l am dancing!
想跟我跳吗？  你跳得好？
You want to dance with me? Are you good?
我跳得好
Yeah, l'm good
我买饮品去
l'm going to get a drink
你懂得跳  我没吹牛
You can dance l don't lie
你不懂
You can't
那我在干什么？
Then what am l doing?
挑逗我的细佬
Teasing my dick
你有潜质，我愿教你
You got potential. l could teach you
不算挑逗吧？
l'm not teasing it now, am l?
当心！
Watch it!
冷静点
Be cool
你才去冷静！
You be cool, buddy!
娜美！
Nomi!
抓着她！
Hey, you! Hold her!
干什么？
What are you doing?
是她惹起的  去死！
She started it! Fuck you!
你玩完
Party's over
娜美
Malone
你可以走
You're out of here
保释文件
Your release papers
如何？
Yo, what's up?
我保释你出来，咖啡也不请喝？
l bailed you out! Don't that get me a cup of coffee?
我只提议教你跳舞
All l said was l'd teach you to dance
谁要你教？
l don't need to be taught that
故此你想对我说：滚蛋，贱种！
Because you're a bad-ass, saying, ''Back off, motherfucker''
对了
You got that down
滚蛋，贱种！
Back off, motherfucker!
你害得我头又痛、细佬又痛…
Know what? My head hurts, my dick hurts...
连饭碗也丢掉
and you got me fired from my job!
认命吧
Shit happens
“认命吧”你只赠我一句警句？
''Shit happens.'' That's what l get? Fucking wisdom?
没有其他？  对，只有警句
That's it?! Yeah, you get wisdom
你不仅要我捱打，也要我受气
You're not just a pain in my head and my dick, you're a pain in my ass
做人难，知吗？
Life sucks, you know?
做人难，认命吧，T恤的标语？
''Life sucks.'' ''Shit happens'' Where you get this, off T-shirts?
我只求你请喝咖啡
All l want is a cup of coffee Yeah?
有两毛半吗？
You got a quarter?
自己去买一杯
Buy yourself a cup
阿尔很生气，说你再旷工的话…
Al is pissed! He says if you miss another night...
你怎出来？  他替我保释
How did you get out? He bailed me out
为什么？
Why?
我踢过他祠堂
l kicked him in the nuts
他喜欢你踢？  必定喜欢
He liked it? He must have
娜美…
Nomi...
我的奶子有胀大吗？
Nomi, do my boobs look bigger to you?
嘉米怀疑自己又怀孕
Carmi thinks she's pregnant again
你又停经？
Girl, you missed your period again?
不知道，似乎没停过
l don't know. l don't think so
大批日本客杀到！
lt's like a Japanese convention out there!
唏，妈咪！
Hey, Mama!
准备好有味笑话没有？
Better get your ''little weenie'' jokes ready
机关又失灵，帮帮忙
This thing ain't working again. Come on!
给我拍一拍
Here we go. Come on
加把劲，再拍一拍！
One more time. Try harder. Harder!
让我试试
Let me try it
这位是喜望
l want you to meet Hope
规矩点，这位是蝶芬妮…
Cut it out. Hope, this is Tiffany...
花拉、希迪、亨莉…
Farrah, Heather, Henrietta...
我叫小仙，不是喜望
My name isn't Hope My name is Penny
小仙不好听，引不起性欲
They want class They don't want to fuck a Penny
客人要操的是希迪、蝶芬妮…
They want to fuck a Heather or a Tiffany
或喜望
Or a Hope
这里讲究气派
This is a class joint
亨莉！
Henry!
各位男嘉宾、及少数的女嘉宾…
Gentlemen, and you few ladies out there
你们期望的波后：亨莉！
what you've been waiting for Henrietta, the Queen of Bazooms!
亨莉！拉高你的裙子！
Hey, Henrietta! Pull your dress up!
你哪是我的对手？这样多肥膏…
Honey, you couldn't handle me With all this fat...
那活宝在哪里，你决找不到
you'd never even find the thing
我向你撒尿，你或找得到
l'd have to piss on you to give you a clue
不够粉红色
You need more pink
谢谢你，希迪
Thanks, Heather
跳过“坐怀舞”没有？
Have you ever done a lap dance before?
说服客人让你跳
You talk them into it
每趟五十元，在后房跳
Fifty bucks a pop, you do it in the back
客人眼看手勿动
Touch and go. They touch, they go
你可摸客人，客人不可摸你
You can touch them They cannot touch you
真好
That's good
胯内射精，可以
lf they come, that's okay
客人拔出来射，你叫巡场来
lf they take it out and come all over you, call the bouncer
若客人肯打赏，无关系
But if he gives you a big tip, then it's okay
明白吗？
Got that?
你，昨晚去了哪里？
And you. Where the fuck were you last night?
我经期到
l was having my period, Al
弄到四处是血…
You didn't want blood everywhere...
你也不想吧？
did you?
没有一句真话，讨厌
l'm getting tired of your shit
你想保住饭碗，就得向我施口技
lf you want to last longer than a week, you give me a blow job
既然受高薪，吃得咸，要抵得渴
First l get you used to the money, then l make you swallow
他是认真的吗？
Was he serious?
猎豹无上装会所
Cheetah's TOPLESS LOUNGE
就是这间
Here we are
你的鼻上沾了点粉
Oh, baby...you missed a spot
那山中种田的汉子…
The farmer in the dell The farmer in the dell
竟然夺去奴家的身子
l had a cherry once, And now it's shot to hell!
下台！下台！
Get off the stage! Get off the stage!
你开口讨人厌！我开口赚人钱！
Shut your hole, honey! Mine's making money!
在男人心目中…
Know what they call...
哪种动物只有一个器官？
that useless piece of skin around a twat?
女人！
A woman!
谢谢捧场！
That's all, folks!
各位来宾…
Ladies and gentlemen...
令你们心痒痒的希迪！
the girl to tickle your pickle! Heather!
菲腊，他说什么？
Phil, what did he say?
他说在美国，人人都是妇科专家
He says in America, everyone's a gynecologist
你喜欢她
You like her?
我喜欢你
l like you
我替你买她私钟
l'll buy her for you
外面有很多豪客，穿上睡袍
We got a bunch of big spenders Put your nightie on
叫他去见鬼
Tell him to go fuck himself
你敢，我赶你走
l'll kick your ass out of here
叫吧，出口气
Tell him. Do yourself a favor
行
Okay
我穿上睡袍
l'll put my nightie on
喝杯酒吗？
Hey! Want a drink?
我叫希迪，想看私人艳舞吗？
l'm Heather. Would you like a private dance with me?
有奶吮吗？
Can l suck your tits?
你不可摸我，我可摸你，好想摸
You can't touch me, but l can touch you l'd like to touch you
我有部份欢迎你摸
l know where you can touch me
什么事？
What's going on?
他们想看她的私人艳舞
They want a private dance with her
好极，过来
So? Great. Get over there
我叫希迪
My name is Heather. Would...
娜美，我喜欢…
Hey, Nomi. l love...
你的指甲，我们想看你私人表演
your nails. We want you to have a private dance with us
只准一个客人看，女性免问
We don't do that One at a time, no women
一百元
A hundred dollars
对不起，夜总会的规矩
Sorry. That's the rule
二百！你向沙克表演，我旁观
Two hundred! You just do Zack and l'll watch
五百
Five hundred
行
Done
我说：行
l said done
坐下来，我去更换音乐
Just sit over there and l'll change the music
什么事？  过瘾的事
What's this about? lt's about fun
你坐在那边…
You sit there...
我坐在这边
and l'll sit here
干什么？
What you doing here?
没什么
Nothing
想看，付钱
You want it, you pay for it
多谢
Thank you
五百元
Five hundred
够快感吗？
Wasn't that fun?
你存心不良
You're such a bitch
但你爱我
But you love me
走得动吧？
Can you walk?
大家晚安，回家歇歇
Good night, girls. Get some rest
去庆祝嘛
Go out. Celebrate
来我处吸大麻
Let's go to my place and smoke dope
你仍有那泰国货？
You still got some of that Thai stuff?
我喜爱骚货，最欣赏腿、腋部份
l love thighs. l get off on them l like armpits, too
去吗？娜美  不去
Want to come, Nomi? Not me
我去
l'll come
你刚赚了五百元
You just got $500 off a lap dance
阿尔，别提了
Al, just stop
一副哭丧嘴脸
You act like somebody died
等一等
Wait. Listen
听我说
Just listen
你舞蹈天份之高，我前所未见
You have more natural dancing talent than anyone l've ever seen
我在纽约拜过名师…
l've seen a lot of dancers.
见过不少人跳舞
l studied in New York. Alvin Ailey
你跳舞时，热力逼人
You burn when you dance
你说过我不懂跳
You said l couldn't
你要学习收敛，跳舞不是性交
You have to learn to hold some in Dancing ain't fucking
又来警句？难道我不知？
ls that more Wisdom? l know that!
你昨晚像和那男人大干特干
You don't. You dance like when you fucked that guy last night
哪个？  有女伴那个
What guy? With the chick
在后房表演
You went in back
我没干他  你有
l didn't fuck him You did
你把男女都干  你跟踪我？
You fucked him and her. You followed me?
我没干过任何人！
l didn't fuck anybody!
我看见！
l saw you!
实际的性交可传染爱滋，你呢？
Everybody got AlDS and shit What is it you think you do?
你在意识上干他们，不妥
You fuck them without fucking them lt ain't right
你太有天份！
You got too much talent!
滚！
Get out of here!
我说的是真话！
Bitch, it's the truth!
要我走？我走好了！
You want me to go? l'm out of here!
我考到A级！
l got an A!
再上四堂课，我就有学位
Four more classes, they have to give me that degree
好极！
Great!
半年来只靠右手自慰
l haven't gotten laid in six months
弄到右手发软，不能执针线
My right hand's so tired, l can't thread a needle
改用左手
Use the left
用左手执针线？
For threading a needle?
好漂亮的裙子
Wow. l like that
我替你缝
l can make that
去买衣料吧
Let's go to the fabric store
我够钱，想买
l want to buy it. l have the money
为什么？
Why?
不知道，总之想买
l don't know. l just do
从没有过这样的裙子
l never had a dress like that
会很适合我
lt'll look great on me
对吗？
Won't it?
认为如何？
What do you think?
哗
Oh, my goodness
裙子很衬你
lt looks quite good on you
不算差劲
lt doesn't suck
我竟然买下来！
l can't believe l bought it!
我请你吃墨西哥薄饼
Come on. l'll buy you a burrito
甚至吃墨西哥火锅也可以
l'll even buy you some...fajitas!
不行，要上早班，阿尔管得很严
Fuck, l can't. l'm on early Al's on my back
别担心，我载你上班
Don't worry. l'll drive you
不得了！
Oh, my God!
他会来！
He's coming here!
你或会见到他 我应说什么？
Maybe you can meet him! What would l say?
说：安德鲁，我连针也执不起来
Say, ''Andrew, l can't even thread a needle anymore''
我儿，来娘亲处！来啊！
Baby, mama's waiting for you! Come to me!
我非买入场票不可
l must get tickets for the concert!
跳多点嘛
Come on, baby
滚开！   对不起
Fuck off! Sorry
记得我吗？
Remember me?
星尘酒店的菲腊
Phil Newkirk, Stardust Hotel
我们的舞蹈团有空缺
There's a spot open in the chorus line
明天的跳舞面试，你应该来
We're auditioning tomorrow You should try out
我？  对，你
Me? Yeah, you
你请我去试舞？
You're asking me?
我看过你跳舞，觉得你适合
When l saw you dance, l thought, Yes!''
她派你来
She sent you
没有人派我来
Nobody sent me
十时到
Be there at ten
露个屁股来看看
l want to see your ass
我参观你的家园，看野牛的出现
Oh, show me a home, where the buffalo roam
你参观我的家园…
And l'll show you a home
到处是粪便！
Full of shit!
多谢
Thank you
慕莉！
Molly!
什么事？
What is it?
我获邀试舞！
l got an audition!
宝丽安妮！
Hey, Pollyanna!
你叫我什么？  你像宝丽安妮
What did you call me? You look like Pollyanna
小姐们！
Okay, ladies!
我叫东尼摩士，节目监制
l'm Tony Moss. l produce this show
你们也许听过，我是个衰人
Some of you may have heard l'm a prick
如假包换的衰人
l am a prick
我只管节目的演出…
l have one interest, and that's the show
不管你们的死活
l don't care if you live or die
我要你们能跳、能笑
l want to see you dance and l want to see you smile
你如果笑容、水准、责相不够…
l can't use you if you can't smile, if you can't show, if you can't sell
对我没用，现在开始检阅
Let me take a look at you
排成一行
Spread out
有没有搞错？瞧这对奶子
Jesus Christ, Marty, take a look at these tits
算什么？西瓜？
What are these, watermelons?
这是舞台，不是果园，再见
This a stage, not a patch. See ya
我见过你
l've seen you before
我一月来面试，你叫我修理鼻子
l auditioned for you in January You told me to get my nose fixed
鼻子不错  谢谢，摩士先生
Nose looks good. Thanks, Mr. Moss
笑容不俗
Nice smile Thanks, Mr. Moss
可惜的是，耳朵兜风
You know what, though? Your ears stick out
修理耳朵后再来
Come back after they're fixed
再见
See ya
能够把MGM反过来读吗？
Can you spell MGM backwards?
MGM  佩服
M-G-M l'm impressed
把娃娃脸干掉，再来
Come back when you've fucked this baby fat off
你的头像网球，须戴假发
l hope you got some wigs, tennis ball
上过什么课程？
What classes have you had?
溜冰、芭蕾舞、爵士舞…
lce skating classes, ballet classes...
爵士舞技巧等课程
jazz classes, jazz technique classes
节目叫“女神”，不是“课程”
This show is called Goddess'''', not ''Classes.''
再见
See ya
有上过课程吗？
What kind of classes have you had?
没有
None
来干什么？
So what are you doing here?
见识你这衰人
Watching you be a prick
你还未开眼界呢
You ain't seen nothing yet
琪！示范舞步
Gay! Show them the routine
大家散开，胜出空位，先拍右腿
Everyone back up, find some space! Start with your right leg, slap it
一、二、三、四！
One, two, three, four!
五、六、七…开始跳
Go! Five, six, seven-hit it!
加把劲！
Slam it!
踢！
Kick it!
踢高！伏下！
And up! Stay down!
大家休息
Relax, you can take a break
网球头、后面的黑发
Tennis ball, dark hair in the back
你好，甜姐儿
Hello, doll
进展如何？   不错
How's it going? Good
好
Okay...
你留下来
l want you to stay
还有你
And you
你也留下
You, too
再见，别枉费你我的时间，列队
Good-bye, ladies. You wasted my time and yours! Line up!
抖出奶子来给我看
Show me your tits
这是无上装演出，抖出奶子来！
l got a topless show! Let me see your tits!
十分不俗
Very nice
不俗，不俗
Very nice, ladies
琪！播音乐！换灯光！
Gay! Start the other music! Change the lights!
播“天使”
Cue ''Angel''
积，加强舞台两旁灯光！
Jack, bring up the side spots!
我要你们显露气势
l want to see some attitude!
小姐们，我要气势！我要责相！
l said attitude! Come on, ladies! Sell!
身体的责相！
Sell your bodies!
停音乐！
Cut it!
试试练瑜伽，倒悬，再见
Try yoga, babe, or hanging from the ceiling. See ya
马狄，冰
Marty, ice
你的乳头有不妥吗？
Something wrong with your nipples?
干吗不坚挺？弄坚挺乳头
They're not sticking up. Stick them up
用手摸摸
Play with them a little bit
捏捏，你要的话，我愿代劳
Pinch them You want me to do it for you, l'll do it
我已经坚挺
l'm erect
你干吗还未坚挺？
Why aren't you erect?
接着，敷冰
Here. Put ice on them
不出所料
l called that right
再见，宝丽安妮！
See ya, Pollyanna!
今日到此为止！谢谢
That's it for today! Thank you
你叫我来试舞，对吗？
You got me the audition, didn't you?
为什么？
Why?
也许我欣赏你的舞技
Maybe l like the way you dance
也许我欣赏你
Maybe l like you
有什么分别？
What difference does it make?
刚才你开心了吧？
Did you enjoy that out there?
算得开心
Yeah, darling, l think l did
我恨你
l hate you
我知道
l know
抹鼻
Wipe your nose
牙医会议的人在那边！
The orthodontist convention is over there!
地产会议二十分后开！
Realtors come in 20 minutes!
你来干什么？
What are you doing here?
刚参加试舞
l just had an audition
想当舞蹈艺员？
You want to be a showgirl?
占士，快去搬行李箱！
Smith, what is this?! Move those bags!
试舞不顺利？
Didn't go too good, huh?
我很高兴
l'm glad
别发伟论，我没心情听！
Just don't, okay? l'm not in the mood!
占士，我在叫你！
Smith, l'm talking to you!
舞蹈团不适合你
You don't want to be in this kind of show
脱衣舞起码担白
At least what you do is honest
观众要看胸臀，你就露胸露臀
They want tits and ass, that's what you give
舞蹈团假充艺术，仍靠露胸露臀
Here, they pretend they want something else, you still show tits and ass
要勾搭她，用你私人时间
You want to work her, work her on your own time
我在跟她谈话
l'm talking to her
我在跟她谈话，并非勾搭她
l said l'm talking to her l'm not working her
你打扰我，很无礼，给我滚！
You're interrupting me and that's rude Get the fuck out of here!
贱种
Asshole
革你职！
You're fired!
拿着！
Take this!
你干的好事，又累我丢工作
Now look what you did. You got me fired again
你的确无可药救，不知羞
You're a real bad-ass. You got no shame
天朗气清、阳光灿烂、财源滚滚
Look what a beautiful day it is. The sun is shining, money's flowing
我要替你解闷，请你吃超级大餐
l'm going to cheer you up. l'll get you the best meal in town
津津有味
You like that burger!
你从哪处来？
Where are you from?
从各处来
Different Places
你倒也乐意公开自己的事
You like talking about you, huh?
什么地方？  我的家
Where are we? My place
来干什么？
Why?
我想给你看点东西
l want to show you something
顶级套房，我千辛万苦才租到
Best suite in town l had to beg and plead to get it
想给我看什么？
This what you wanted me to see?
什么事？这张大床？
What? This nice, big bed here?
这首曲我为你而作
l wrote this number. lt's about you
你对我一无所知
You know nothing about me
我知你肯私人表演
l know you're a private dancer
凑足三个舞娘就行
l only need three other girls
我们可到殷殷会所登台
We can put it on at the Crave Club
让我示范
l'll show you
站在这里看
Stand right here. Watch me
慢点！这样吗？
Wait a minute, slow down! Like this?
跟我跳，你跟得上
Follow me. l know you can
我有月经
l have my period
还用说
Yeah, right
摸一摸
Check
对吧？
See?
可以垫毛巾
lt's okay, l got towels
你爱我时才跟我干
You can fuck me when you love me
那样，我爱你！
Then l do love you!
不消说
Yeah, right
你骗不了我，我看穿你
You don't fool me. l see you
看穿什么？
What do you see?
你有所隐瞒
l see you hiding
瞒谁？
From what?
瞒自己
From you
你有过不愉快的经历
You got into some bad shit somewhere
谢谢汉堡包
Thanks for the hamburger!
东尼叫你立即覆电话，拨这号码
Tony Moss called. He said to call him right away. Here's the number
打给他！好心你，我打
Call him! Oh, Jesus. l'll call him
我叫娜美，想找东尼
Tony Moss, please. lt's Nomi Malone
录用了我
l got it
这德州黄玫瑰，每趟五十元收费
She's the yellow rose of Texas, she charges 50 bucks
她发的大财，都靠床上苦干得来
She's the richest girl in Texas, and all she does is fucks!
你迟到 不会再到，另有工作
You're late. l'm gone. l got another job
改投另一间会所？
Where? You going to another club?
有更高的分账？我照付
You getting a better cut? l'll match it
我去参加星尘的“女神”演出
l'm in ''Goddess'', at the Stardust
有什么好笑？
What's so fucking funny?
她转投星尘，参加舞蹈演出
She's going down to the Stardust! She's in the show
可喜可贺
Well, good for her!
她会回来
She'll be back
我决不回来！
No, l won't. l'll never come back!
你是脱衣舞娘，怎不自量？
You're a stripper. Don't you get it?
我是舞蹈员！
l'm a dancer!
你是舞蹈员，亨莉就是圣母！
lf you're a dancer, Henry here's the Virgin Mary!
比起圣母，我更大胸、更多口！
l got bigger tits than the Virgin Mary, and a bigger mouth, too!
唯有你能替我修理那露乳机关
Damn it. You're the only one who gets my tits popping right
再见，阿尔
See ya, Al!
我不会再雇用你
l'm not hiring you back, hear me?
即使你为我吹箫！
Not even if you give me a fucking blow job!
占士！
James!
开门！
Come on!
我已被录用！
l got it!
参加“女神”演出
l'm in the show! ln ''Goddess''
我为你作的曲呢？
What about the number l wrote?
还以为我们会合作
l thought we were working on something
占士
James?
你也为她作曲？
She's in your number?
等一等！
l'll be right there!
她不懂跳舞
She can't dance
但你会教她，对吗？
But you'll teach her, right?
她有天份，对吗？
She's got talent, right?
你我间没有瓜葛
You and me, we ain't got no ties
跳舞不是性交，对吗？
Dancing ain't fucking. Right?
对…
Yeah...that's right
再见
See ya
那是谁？
Who was that?
想合作跳舞的人
Someone who wanted to be in the number
你不会用她取代我吧？
You're not giving her my part, are you?
不会，她不懂跳舞
Nah, baby. She can't dance
那首曲我为你而作
l wrote that number for you, you know that
对不起
Excuse me
什么贵干？
Can l help you?
我叫娜美，来见摩士先生
l'm here to see Mr. Moss Nomi Malone
可以进去
Okay. Go on in
她那天看似倔强的宝丽安妮…
One day she looks like Pollyanna
今天看似诱人的罗烈蒂
the next she looks like l don't know, Lolita
不俗的裙子
Nice dress
我在华茜买的
Thanks. l bought it at Ver-sayce
富林商场
ln the Forum?
对了，我喜欢华茜
Oh, yeah, Ver-sayce. l love Ver-sayce
我也是
Me, too
你认识马狄吧
Okay, you know Marty
琪是领队
Gay is our line captain
我这超级衰人的声誉，得来不易
lf you let me down, l'll lose reputation for being an all-knowing prick
别教我失望，令我声誉受损
l worked very hard for that reputation, so don't do it.
同意吗？
Deal?
同意
Deal
琪会介绍情形
Gay will show you around
跟我来
Let's go
娜美，我们今午练舞
Nomi? We'll do a run-through this afternoon
祝你好运
Good luck
赌场赢你钱前，先祝你好运
They tell you that here just before taking your money
你得保持身材，吃赤米、蔬菜
You must maintain your weight Eat brown rice and vegetables
避开阳光，以免晒成两截色
And stay indoors Tan lines aren't allowed
化妆服饰由你保管，不得带回家
Make-up and costumes are your responsibility. Don't take them home
千万不要在台上哭泣
And don't ever, ever go out onstage crying
你吃赤米、蔬菜吧？
You do eat brown rice and vegetables, don't you?
好
Good
你的化妆台
This is your table
你像我那样理智的话…
lf you're smart, and l was smart...
为自己的事业、对象，及早铺路
you'll figure out a job and man for later on
你怎找到对象？
How'd you find your guy?
我补牙时，结识了那牙医
l chipped my tooth on a Quaalude He was my dentist
你每晚上落楼梯六次
You'll run this monster 6 times a night
紧握扶手，我带你去人事部
Hold onto the railing. l'll take you to personnel
人事部要资料
They want some information
什么资料？
What kind of information?
出生日期
Date of birth
七三年七月三日
1973/7/3
出生地点
Place of birth
纽约
New York
纽约市？
New York, New York?
亲人
Nearest family members
无亲无故
l don't have family
都去世？
Deceased?
是
Yes
曾被捕？有案底？
Have you ever been arrested? Charged with a criminal offense?
没有
No
福利证件号码？
Social Security number
不知道，待我查出后，告诉你
l don't know Let me check on that for you, okay?
你受录用！好极！
You got it! Nice going!
沙克，这位是娜美
That's great. Zack, this is Nomi Malone
我记得，你好
l remember her. Hi
你当然记得
l bet you do
相当难忘，欢迎加入，漂亮的裙
She's pretty memorable. l'm glad you're part of the team. Nice dress
华茜的时装
lt's a Ver-sayce
“华莎姿”
lt's Versace
应该读作“华莎姿”
lt's Versace. lt's pronounced Ver-sa-chee
你够品味、够美貌
You have a great taste. You look beautiful
小姐们！
Girls!
这位是娜美
This is Nomi!
妮奇、茱莉、甸娜，琪你已认识
Nicky, Julie, Deena and you know Gay
她们示范，你旁观
They'll run through it. You watch
吃过东西没有？
Did you eat?
积！吃什么？
Jack! What do you want?
汉堡、薯条、梳打
Burger, fries and soda
替她买赤米、蔬菜、矿泉水
Get her some brown rice, vegetables and an Evian
不，先看示范
No, Nomi, come take a look at this
准备！五、六、七、八！
Here we go! Five, six, seven, eight!
轮到你，准备…
You try it now. Ready?
五、六、七，开始！
Go! Five, six, seven, hit it!
踢！加把劲！
Kick it! Work it!
停！那是什么转身？
Hold it! Nomi, what kind of turn was that?
足尖旋转，转吧
Do a pique turn. Come on
对了，音乐！
That's it. Okay, music!
来吧！
Go! Hah! Go!
高点
Higher
不要那样高
Not that high
配合音乐节奏！
Stay in sync!
一，二，三，一
One, two, three, one!
挺！挺！
Thrust it! Thrust it!
Thrust it! Come on!
够了，谢谢各位
Okay! That's enough. Thank you, ladies
干得好
Good job
要她多练转身，留意身体平衡
Work on her turns. l'm worried about her balance
我几时开始表演？
How long before l can do the show?
今晚开始
You start tonight
今晚？  你应付得来
Tonight? You'll be fine
她的表现如何？
How did she do?
并非花拳绣腿
She's no butterfly
腰有挺劲，浑身野性
She's all pelvic thrust. She prowls. She's got it
哪处来的野性？
l wonder how she got it?
不是学来的
She didn't learn it
是学来的，但并非从课堂学来
She learned it, but it's not taught in any class
多点橙色，我替你涂
You need more orange. Let me do it
觉得怎样？
How do you feel?
不要问！
Don't ask. Don't ask!
我的化妆品呢？
Who took my make-up?
猩猩来了！
Monkey alert! Monkey alert!
早叫你看管猩猩！
Damn it, Hector! l told you!
猩猩春情动，要生孩子！
They get the heat! They make babies!
孩子？
Babies?
赶出去
Oh, get it out
小心
Watch it
走！   抓着那猩猩！
Go! Go! Grab her!
我抓着一头！
Hey! l got one!
其余在楼上
The rest are upstairs
淫妇，不准再碰我的化妆品！
Julie, you slut, don't touch my make-up!
淫妇？你操那送外卖的小子！
l'm a slut? You fucked that pizza place kid!
你操那抄表汉子！
You fucked the meter reader!
泼货！   你活得不耐烦
Bitch! You're fucking dead!
安妮，停手
Jesus, Annie, get off her!
茱莉，冷静点
Julie! Calm down! Stop it!
打架到此为止
Now settle down! lt's done!
够钟演出
Showtime
去！四个八拍！
Move! You got four counts of eight!
等一等，假发
Nomi, wait. Your wig
你应付得来，大家上去！
You're fine. Let's move up, you guys!
舞台上有粪便
There's shit on the stage
猩猩吃完蒜头总拉粪
They always shit. lt's that garlic
粪便在哪？  左后边
Where? Top left
左后舞台有猩猩粪，去！
Upstage left, monkey shit. Let's go!
吸点可卡因吗？
Want some blow?
敷冰的最后机会
Last chance for ice
快！
Let's go!
快！快！
Go, go, go, go!
我爱你
l love you
大家快点！娜美，跑！
Come on, you guys, keep it moving! Run, Nomi!
等一等！
Nomi, wait!
第二拍，一、二…去！
Two beats. One, two...go!
妈的
Shit
各位，星尘隆重介绍姬丝桃小姐
Ladies and gentlemen, the Stardust presents Miss Cristal Connors
有两分钟，戴上红发，我取服装
You got two mins. Put on your red wig l'll get your costume
祝顺利，沙克
Good luck. Love, Zack Carey
娜美，穿上去
Nomi. Slip this on
我表现如何？   好
Did l do okay? You did fine
伸腿须改善，明天中午来练舞
Your leg extension needs work. Someone will work with you. Be here at noon
戴上去，行
Put this on. You're done
我没摔倒  差点摔倒
l didn't fall. You nearly fell
喂！
Hey, yo!
谈谈行吗？
Can l talk to you a minute?
求求你
Come on, please?
谈吧
Talk
单独谈
Alone?
我去开车  我很快来
l'll get the car. Be right there
谁送的花？
Who sent you the flowers?
不关你事
None of your business
我只想说…
Okay. l just wanted to say...
你我间没有瓜葛
You and me ain't got no ties
我承认好色
l have a problem with pussy
一向如此，改不了
l always have, and l always will
但我言出由衷
But l meant what l said
我才不管 那首曲确为你而作
l don't care about your problems. l did write it for you
但我答应过教她，也搞上她
But l did tell her l would teach her, and l did fuck her
你搞上谁是你的事，不关我事
Who you fuck is your business l won't make it mine
那首曲既然赚不了钱…
lt's not like l'm seeing any money for writing that number
我顺便用来泡女人
l may as well touch a little pussy
你没话说？
You got nothing to say
是
No
谢谢你的花
Thanks for the flowers!
东尼赞你跳得好
Tony said you did great!
我从没接过花
l never got flowers before
我肯定陆续有来
l'm sure you'll get lots of them
他送的花？
He gave them to you?
对
Yeah, he did
干什么职业？扯皮条？
What is he? A pimp?
那是部扯皮条型的汽车
Only people with pimp cars are pimps
他是娱乐总监
He's the entertainment director
果然是扯皮条
That's what l said. He's a pimp!
我们走吧
Let's go!
祝你好运
Good luck with your number
喂
Hello?
有人吗？
Anybody here?
观众席这里
Back here
你来干什么？
What are you doing here?
我来干什么？
What am l doing here?
来吸世间最好的可卡因，要吗？
Doing some of the finest cocaine in the world. Want some?
舒筋活络妙品
lt's great for the muscles
我对马狄说，会教你转身…
l told Marty l'd work on turns with you...
但现在有点不舒服
but l'm feeling a little inside-out
废话少说
Cut the shit
好吧
Okay
你我一直有点误会
We got off on the wrong foot
不记前嫌，和解如何？
Want to start dancing all over again?
为什么和解？
Why?
为什么不和解？
Why not?
去史柏高吃午餐吗？
Want to go eat at Spago?
在哪里？
Where is it?
在华茜附近
Just down from Ver-sayce
华莎姿
Versace
对，华莎姿
Ahh, right. Versace
请享用
Enjoy
什么东西？
What is all this stuff?
我替你点菜
l'll order for you
我要赤米、蔬菜
l'll have brown rice and vegetables
你喜欢赤米、蔬菜？
Do you like brown rice and vegetables?
喜欢吃？
You do?
可算喜欢
Sort of
真的？
Really?
比狗粮难吃
lt's worse than dog food
的确难吃
lt is
我吃过狗粮
l've had dog food
你吃过？
You have?
好久以前
A long time ago
狗饼
Doggy chow
我以前喜欢吃狗饼
l used to love Doggy Chow
我也是
l used to love Doggy Chow, too
喝香槟我会头痛
l got a headache from champagne
这不是香槟
This isn't champagne
是姬丝桃牌圣水
This is holy water
我艺名的出处
l named myself after this holy water
我原本叫姬丝，褐发、小乳房
Chrissie Lou Connors had dingy brown hair and little tits
化妆、隆胸后，脱胎换骨
lt's amazing what paint and a surgeon can do
你的整容一流
You have great tits
养眼
They're beautiful
过奖
Thank you
我欣赏美观的乳房
l like nice tits
一向都欣赏，你呢？
l always have. What about you?
我喜欢有美观的乳房
l like having nice tits
你爱怎样包装？
How do you like having them?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你明白我的意思
You know what l mean
我爱穿漂亮的裙子…
l like having them in a nice dress...
或紧身上衣
or a tight top
你喜欢露胸
You like to show them off
我不喜欢在猎豹露
l didn't like showing them at the Cheetah
为什么？
Why not?
我跟所有观众一样欣赏
l liked looking at them there. Everybody did
我觉得像娼妓
lt made me feel like a hooker
你是娼妓啊
You are a whore, darling
我不是
l'm not!
我们都是
We all are
我们赚钱，全靠迎合观众的爱好
We take the cash, we cash the check, we show them what they want to see
也许你是娼妓，我不是
Maybe you're a whore, but l'm not
你与我…
You and me...
都是同一种人
we're exactly alike
我怎也不会似你
l'll never be like you
姬小姐，麻烦你签个名，行吗？
Miss Connors! Sorry to bother you Would you sign this for me?
乐意，大名是什么？
Happy to. What's your name?
法兰，来自德州
Frank. l'm from Galveston
我也是德州人
l'm from Del Rio myself, Frank
我早说过她是德州人，瞧！
l told you she was from Texas. Whoo-ee, look at that!
也替我签，行吗？
Could l have one like that?
你不想印干我的口红吧？
You want a girl to use up all her lipstick on you?
想跳舞吗？   现在跳？
Want to dance? Right now?
正如猫王那首歌：“机不可失”
lt's now or never. That's what Elvis said
我听过句金石良言…
You know the best advice l ever got?
你渴望得到一个舞台空缺…
You're up there onstage, hoping on a spot
不妨把所有对手，逐个踩下台
lf someone gets in your way, step on them
最后剩下你，空缺非你莫属
lf you're the only one left standing there, they hire you
我想说的已说完，谢谢
That's about it. Thank you and good night
到此为止
Elvis has left the building
亲爱的，看吧…
You see, darling...
你是娼妓
you are a whore
贱人！
Bitch!
大概已闹翻
Guess we're done
妮奇，我有话跟你说
Nicky, can l talk to you for a second?
妈，看猴子行吗？  现在不行
Mommy, can we see the monkeys? Not now
求求你  猴子要工作
Please. They're so cute. They have to work
什么工作？
What are they doing?
我要看猴子！   现在不行
l want to see the monkeys! Not now
为什么？
Why not?
赶他妈的小孩出去
Get these fucking kids out of here
你说粗口！她说粗口
You said the F'' word! She said the ''F'' word''
她说粗口
She said the F'' word!''
他妈的闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
不要怕
lt's okay. lt's okay
下星期本城举行游艇展览会
Nomi, a boat convention's coming into town next week
要两位小姐，妮奇愿去
They need two girls. Nicky's doing it
你呢？工资一千元
You interested? lt pays $1,000
一千元？干什么？
A thousand dollars? To do what?
替酒店宣传，花枝招展地拍照
Represent the hotel. You wear your costume, smile, they take your picture
一千元？
A thousand dollars?
好极，姬丝桃推荐你
Great. Cristal here recommended you
谢谢
Thanks
别客气，我总会关照你
My pleasure, darling. Just looking out for you
杂志的特写… 稍后才理会
Cristal, about the magazine layout...? Later
不要干
Don't do it
一千元，为什么不干？
lt's $1,000. Why not?
慕莉，来！
Molly, l need you!
来了，干过的小姐都不…
l'm coming. l know girls who did it and they...
慕莉，我在等着！
Molly, l'm waiting
她们都不高兴
They didn't like it
你干过没有？
Did you do it before?
喜欢吗？
Did you like it?
我喜欢吗？喜欢啊
Did l like it? Sure, l liked it
两位在女神中演出的佳丽，谢谢
Let's thank these 2 beautiful girls from Goddess'', a new smash at the Stardust''
倒霉
Shit
情况怎样？   好
How's it going? Fine
苦差，对吗？
Tough gig, huh?
对极
Very
我的老友，曼谷来的兴田先生
This is my good friend, Mr. Okida, from Bangkok
他是我们赌场的大豪客
He's one of our very, very high rollers
表演完后，肯赏面一同进餐吗？
Ladies, we want to take you to dinner after the show
吃龙虾，听凯撒唱歌
Have some lobster, hear Caesar sing
听过凯撒唱歌吗？保证悦耳
You ever heard Caesar sing? The guy's great. You'll love him
凯撒唱歌？
Caesar sing?
然后回我家，我们也唱歌
Then we'll go back to my place and we'll sing
只有我们四人唱
Just the four of us
如何？
How about it?
我们唱歌
We sing
对，大展歌喉
Yeah, we'll sing a lot of songs
行
Okay
好极
Good deal
好，好极
Okay. Good deal
恕不奉陪
Not me
识趣点嘛  放手！
Be nice. Let go of me!
这差事有一千元
You got $1,000 for this
对，这展览会！
Yeah, for this! This!
算了
Oh, forget it
生什么气？没碰过你一根头发！
Just forget it! No harm done! No damage!
哼！
Christ!
沙克
Zack?
我想跟你谈谈
l want to talk to you
上楼去吧
Let's go upstairs
今日开心吗？
Have a nice day, darling?
不
No
可惜
l'm sorry to hear that
离谱
Jesus
对不起，有些人真不知所谓
l'm sorry. Some people just don't get it
我在台上，叫菲腊来
l'm on the stage. Get me Phil
谢谢
Thank you
不要走开
Stay
吃角子机进账增33%
The drop is up 33% on those machines
即是说，每部进账250元归本
lt will make your bottom line about 250
我慿这工作获MBA
l got an MBA for this
现在注重的是，成本分析
That's what this business is now cost analyzing slot machines
MBA是什么？
What's an MBA?
沙克，你在吗？
Zack, you in here?
失陪
Excuse me
唏！什么事？
Hey! What's going on?
再有下趟，你另谋高就
You do anything like this again, you're fired
什么也没发生  还强辩？
Nothing happened. Something did!
她未搞清楚就乱跳
She jumped to conclusions
下趟，轮到你跳：请你跳槽
lt happens again, you'll jump to your conclusion
休想有遣散费
Without your golden parachute
还不向她道歉？
You owe her an apology
娜美，对不起
Nomi, l'm sorry. l apologize
好吧
Yeah, fine. Okay
滚
Get out
MBA是工管硕士，没实际用场
An MBA is a college degree. lt's mostly worthless in the real world
你雄心勃勃
You go for it, don't you?
我尽力而为
Yeah, l try to
够钟演出
Showtime
的确
That's for sure
菲腊你这饭桶，回来
Phil, you dumb fuck, get back up here
知道、知道
l know, l know
谢谢你的关照，向菲腊推荐我
Thank you for looking out for me. You were so nice to recommend me to Phil
我们是朋友嘛
What are friends for?
对
Right
展览会的事，你说得对
You were right about the convention
甜姐儿
Sweet baby!
你再摸，我扭断你的手指！
Do that again, l'll break your fingers!
没法，只有我对异性有兴趣
Not my fault you don't have a gay partner
操你
Fuck you
他拼命宣传自己是异性恋
He wants everyone to see how hetero he is
拿电筒照照他的行头多大
Molly, bring that flashlight so l can see how big it is
想吃老拳吗？
You want a knuckle sandwich?
我用后门吃，行吗？
Can l have mine anally, please?
别吵了！离谱
Come on, you guys! Jesus!
列队准备！
Let's go! Let's line it up!
望什么？贱人
What you looking at, bitch?
快点！去！
Okay, let's go. Move it! Go, go, go!
糟糕
Oh, my God
伤了哪处？安妮
Are you okay, Annie?
我的腿
lt's my leg
哪处痛？
Tell me when it hurts
她的膝盖
lt's her knee
碎了，对吗？
lt isn't broken, is it?
什么回事？
Daryl, what happened?
我一时脚滑
My foot went out from under me
是这一回事
This is what happened
怎会在舞台上出现？
l wonder how those got up here?
或许从服饰脱落
Probably came off a costume
我们送你入院
We'll get you to the hospital
好痛
Shit, no!
可怜的安妮，多倒霉
Jesus. Poor Annie. Tough break
请挪开
Let us through here
稍后见
See you later
我是监制
l'm the producer
你是我雇员，听我命令
l hired you! You do what l say
安妮是我的候补，我有发言权
She was my understudy. l have a say, too
但决策权不在你处
Yeah, but guess who makes the decision
她的膝盖碎了
lt's broken, kids
惨，要三个月才复原
Shit. That will be three months
起码
At least
报应
Bad karma, huh?
娜美，你妈妈在等你
Nomi, your mother's waiting for you
我的妈妈？
My mother?
为你着想，我希望她不是
For your sake, l hope she's not
醒睡的人易睡醒…
lf a light sleeper sleeps with a light on
挺硬的人可硬挺？
Can a hard sleeper sleep with a hard on?
雌老虎哪处厉害？两个吃人的口
What do you call a tiger? A big pussy that eats people
亨莉！
Henry!
吻出口水，好过喷出口水
l can get shit on, but l don't like getting spit on
阿尔
Hi, Al
你难看极
You look like shit
十吋阳具也不及她好看
She looks better than a 10-inch dick and you know it
在这里…工作开心吗？
So...do you like it here?
难道她会怀念你？
What, you think she misses you?
有什么稀奇？
Yeah, why not?
我们怀念她
We miss her
她怀念我们，像我怀念我那痔疮
She misses us like that lump on my twat l had taken off last week
离谱
Jesus, Henry
我们看过你演出
We saw the show
你跳得精彩
You were good
谢谢你，阿尔
Thank you, Al
的确精彩
Real good
保重，小姑娘
You take care, kid
你没有引死人，着实奇怪
Must be weird, not having anyone come on you
娜美，要我载吗？
Nomi. Hey, you want a ride?
我已有人载
l got one
等一等！
Wait!
坐过这汽车吗？
Ever been in one of these?
不
No
我梦寐以求的事
l always wanted one
不同凡响吧？   不算差劲
lt's some car, huh? lt doesn't suck
往哪处去？你带路
Where are we headed? Give me directions
往你家去
To your place
你爱喝姬丝桃香槟？
Do you like Cristal?
我爱喝各种香槟
l like a lot of different champagnes
但我只喝香槟
But l always drink champagne
安德鲁是怎样的人？
What's Andrew Carver like?
你紧张？毋须紧张
Are you nervous? Don't be
我没有紧张
l'm not
我喜欢你的高潮
l liked it when you came
喜欢你的眼睛
l liked your eyes
留下来
Stay with me
早上我载你回去
l'll drive you back in the morning
现在是早上
lt is morning
请留下来
Please?
我已叫计程车
l have a taxi coming
取消好了
Send it back
姬丝桃要位新候补
Cristal needs a new understudy
中午试舞，可有兴趣？
There's an audition at noon. You want to try?
我不来这里，你会告诉我吗？
Would you have told me if l hadn't come here?
提议来的是你，不是我
lt was your idea to come here, not mine
我想再见你
l want to see you again
看情形才说
We'll see how it goes
看什么情形？试舞？
What, the audition?
十元半
Ten-fifty
喂！
Hello!
恨死你
l hate you
对方是谁？   沙克
Who was he? Zack
还得了
Oh, my God
有没有缚起他？
Did you tie him up?
惨
Oh, shit
我忘记解开他
l forgot to untie him
吸毒吸醉了？
Are you high?
有点
Maybe a little
不能睡，中午要试舞，麦片呢？
l can't go to sleep. l have an audition at noon. Where are the Sugar Snaps?
在柜里，娜美…
ln the cupboard. Nomi...
不要上毒瘾
don't get sucked into it
看我找到什么！
Look what l found!
随便你好了
Okay, whatever, Nomes
我选茱莉
Julie
她不够性感  她舞步熟练
She's not hot enough. She has it down
但没有姬丝桃的热力
You can teach it. She doesn't have Cristal's heat
谁也没有
None of them have Cristal's heat
教我怎不爱你
l do love you, Gay
娜美有热力
Nomi has heat
有吗？
Does she?
娜美有
Yes, she does
完全不同的热力
ln a totally different way
说笑！由她当主角？
Come on! She's going to take the lead?
这是大型节目，不是脱衣舞！
This a hotel show! lt's not the Cheetah!
不要紧，八年来我从未失场
lt doesn't matter l haven't missed a show in 8 years
你不会愈来愈年轻
You're not getting any younger
狗种
Eat me
看娜美试舞吗？  不
Want to see it again with just Nomi? No
我看，去准备吧
l do. Set it up, Marty
不知所谓
This is bullshit
假公济私
lt's about your dick
妮奇、茱莉，谢谢
Nicky, Julie, thank you!
有她的资料吗？
What do we know about her?
全无，连福利证号码也不可靠
Nothing. l doubt her Social Security number's right
调查她   查什么？
Find out. What?
一切
Everything
你与她有一手？
You fucked her, didn't you?
你生气，因为妒忌？抑或…
Are you pissed off because you're jealous?
因为被我捷足先登？
Or because l beat you to the punch?
你操他，为空缺？抑或为兴趣？
You fuck him for the spot or because you wanted to?
我相信，你为空缺
l say you did it for the spot
你惯用身体作交易？
ls that what you did, Cristal?
我们既是朋友，激怒我对你无益
You don't want to piss me off, now that we're friends
你不应动怒
No, you shouldn't get pissed off
动怒令你衰老
lt makes you look older
你升为候补
You got it
真的？
l do?
马狄与琪会教你
Marty and Gay will work with you
菲腊会安排宣传，你干得好
Phil will have some glossies taken. You did good
我们一起进餐、吃龙虾
l'll call you for dinner, lobster
听过凯撒唱歌吗？保证悦耳
Did you ever hear Caesar sing? You'll love it
望什么？
What?
恭喜，原来你多才多艺
Congratulations. l see you have many talents
我认为她跳得好
l thought she did good
殷殷会所 占士舞蹈演出
A Private Dance By James Smith The Crave Club
事后我才知道试舞的事
l didn't know about the audition until afterwards
我的指甲怎样？
Do you like my nails?
比不上你的漂亮
They're not as nice as yours
也许有空我替你修甲
Maybe l'll help you with yours sometime
你愿意的话
lf you want
你真好人
lsn't that nice of you, darling?
我们是朋友嘛
What are friends for?
想深一层…
On second thought...
也许不应让你修甲
maybe you shouldn't do mine
我太老，不适合婊子打扮
l'm getting too old for that whory look
我会考虑一下
l'll think about it
出去时关门
Close the door on your way out
不懂跳舞，不要假充！
Hey, bring on the real dancers!
嘘！
Boo!
差劲！
You suck!
下台！
Get off the stage!
表演够了！
Enough of this stuff!
我们跳舞吧！
Let's dance!
好看、出色
l loved it! lt was good
你来，不怕失身份？
What are you doing here, slumming?
希迪！
Heather!
我们怎样？
Were we good?
好极
Great
她跳得笨手笨脚
She dances like a truck!
怎会！要喝东西吗？
l do not! Do you want something to drink?
来杯啤酒，婆娘
Yeah. Get me a beer, bitch
看我的戒指
Look what l got
真美
lt's beautiful
我从祖母处偷来
l stole it from my grandmother
不是！你从当铺处买
You did not! You got it at a pawnshop
我们快结婚
We're getting married
你爱她？
You love her?
不知道，奉子成婚
l don't know. She's having a baby
演出呢？
And this?
不受欢迎，观众喝倒采
We ain't any good. You heard them. ''Get off the stage!''
有什么打算？
What will you do?
帮外母打理杂货店
Work in a grocery store Her mother owns it
婴儿食物我们有折扣
We'll get a discount on baby food
再见
See ya
认命吧、做人难，对我用得上
Shit happens, you know? Life sucks. l'm a student of T-shirts!
妮奇
Hey, Nicky
娜美小姐…
Dear Ms. Malone,
我们不能选你为后补…万分遗憾
We regret we are unable to offer you...understudy
不准进去！
You can't go in there!
什么事？
What's going on?
“什么事？”
What's going on?!
冷静点   “冷静点”！
Hey, cool it. Cool it?!
竟发这封信来！
When you sent me this?!
她用离职威胁，出动律师
She threatened to walk! She got her lawyers into it!
又如何？
So what?!
她是个明星！你及不上
So, she's a star! You're not worth it
对不起，娜美，我已尽力
Sorry, Nomi. l tried. Fuck!
绳胯断掉，我赤裸裸跳足五分钟
Basically, my G-string snapped. There l was, dancing butt naked for 5 mins
难为了我的舞伴
l mean, my poor partner!
我考虑过，亲爱的
l thought about it, darling
现在替我修甲，行吗？
Think you could do my nails now?
行
Okay
或许改天吧
Maybe some other time
随我来…女奴隶
Come on...slave girl
五分钟后出场，快！
We've got five minutes. Go!
大家赶快！
Go, you guys! Run, run!
让路！
Let me through!
惨！
Shit!
姬丝桃，你听见我吗？
Cristal, can you hear me?
叫马狄来！
Somebody get Marty!
什么事？   不知道
What happened? l don't know
召救伤车！
Somebody get an ambulance!
谁在她后面？
Who was behind her?
我
l was
发生什么事？
What happened?
不知道，她突然摔下去
l don't know. She just went down
滑倒，我看到
She slipped. l saw it
娜美离她很远
Nomi wasn't even close to her
多倒霉
Tough break, huh?
什么事？
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing
谢谢，有消息请通知我
Thanks. Keep me informed
她脑部受震盪，无大礙
She has a concussion. That'll be all right
但臀部严重断骨
But she has a compound fracture of the hip
康复极费时日
Those take forever to heal
必须关闭
We have to shut down
无论如何得表演下去
Not a chance. The show goes on
星尘是不夜天，从没试过关闭
The Stardust is never dark. lt has never been
只要我活着，决不关闭
lt never will be. Not while l am alive
谁是后补？
Who was her understudy?
我们有位小姐…
We had a girl who...
笑什么？
What's funny?
姬丝桃是位明星，无可取代
Cristal Connors is a star, Sam! You can't just replace her
我们聘人暂代，等她康复
We could bring someone in while she's out
可能要等一年
She could be out for a year
聘谁？
Like who?
珍纳积逊、宝拉阿都
Janet Jackson. Paula Abdul
上我的节目？
Paula Abdul? ln my show?
酬金过巨，我们付不起
We're not paying those kind of salaries
既然如此，我们依照赌城作风…
ln that case, Mr. Karlman, we do what we do in Vegas
博一博
We gamble
各位来宾
Ladies and gentlemen...
星尘郑重介绍：娜美小姐
the Stardust proudly presents Miss Nomi Malone
我们谁也雇得起
We could have hired anyone
珍纳积逊、宝拉阿都
Janet Jackson, Paula Abdul
赌城的魅力，集于娜美一身
Nomi Malone is what Las Vegas is all about
她光芒四射、美艳动人…
She's dazzling, she's exciting...
十分性感，谢谢你，沙克
...and very, very sexy. Thank you, Zack
觉得今晚的演出怎样？
How did you feel about the show tonight?
我希望能够胜任
l hope l can be as good as the show
你胜任有余，本节目全靠你
You are, my dear. You are the show
望过来，娜美
Good one. Over here, Nomi
再来一张！麻烦你
One more, Nomi! Please, please
有派对，准备好未？
Hey, you ready to party?
哪里？  我租下天堂酒店
Where? The Paradiso. l rented the bungalows
为谁开？   为你
For what? For you
快，豪华房车接送
Hurry. l got a limo waiting
我没有适合的衣服  你有
l don't have anything to wear! Yes, you do
安德鲁也去，他欣赏你的演出
Andrew Carvers' coming He saw the show and thinks you're great
听到吗？安德鲁也会去！
Did you hear? Andrew Carver will be there!
听到了
Yeah. l heard
什么事？
What's wrong with you?
你推她下去
You pushed her, didn't you?
没有
No
你怎可这样说？茱莉见到
How can you say that to me? Julie saw it
不可能，她当时背向你，我在场
She couldn't have seen it. l saw Julie and her back was to you
她见到
She saw it
算了
Okay
祝你派对开心
Have fun at your party
去嘛，不去怎行？安德鲁也去
Come here, Molly! You have to come Andrew will be there
我不管
l don't care
没你，派对没意思
lt ain't a party without you
放手
Let go of me
放手！
Let go of me!
献给这世上独一无二的美女！
To the one and only beautiful girl in the world
等一等
One minute
犀利
Oh, my God
我想知道的是…
So, what l want to know is...
安德鲁在哪里？
where's Andrew?
看
Look
女神娜美
Nomi Malone Goddess
真羡慕你的打扮
l love your outfit
娜美…我可以做你的候补吗？
Nomi... you think l could be your understudy?
我会考虑
l'll see what l can do
谢谢你
Thanks, darling
安德鲁到了，我来介绍
Andrew Carver's here. l want to introduce you
安德鲁到了！
Andrew's here!
安德鲁…娜美
Andrew Carver...Nomi Malone
精彩的演出
You were sensational tonight
过奖  哪里
Thank you. And you're welcome
在哪处发掘她？
Where did you find her?
军事秘密
l'll never tell
我喜欢你的歌
l like your songs
我喜欢你的屁股，打电话给我
And l like your ass. Call me
慕莉…
Molly Abrams...
安德鲁
Andrew Carver
我连针也执不起来
l can't even thread a needle anymore
什么？
Sorry?
慕莉是你的忠实歌迷
Molly's one of your biggest fans
既然如此…我替你倒杯酒
Well, then...let me get you a drink
随我来
Come on
玩得开心点
Enjoy
你今日多美
You look beautiful tonight
什么事？
What's going on?
耍乐一下
Just want to party, baby
放手！
Let me go!
抓住她
Get her!
放手！   他妈的闭嘴！
Let me go! Shut the fuck up!
扔她上床！
Throw her down!
干她！
Fuck her!
干她吧！
Fuck her, man
干她！
Fuck her! Fuck her!
放开我！
Let me go!
干她！
Fuck her!
我可能爱上你
l could fall in love with you
我们走吧
Let's get out of here
慕莉
Molly?
她受惊过度，已注射镇定剂
We have her sedated. She's in shock
鼻樑折断、阴道破裂
She has a broken nose, vaginal tears
要留医三、四日
She'll be here three or four days
沙克！
Zack!
看这个
Look at this
还有这个，稍后见
And look at this. Later
警察呢？   不会来
Where are the police? They're not here
为什么？   不来就不来
Why not? Because they're not coming!
不要报警…
Don't do it...
宝丽
Polly
你怎知道？
How did you find out?
你曾在殷殷会所被捕
You were busted at a fight at the Crave Club
警方有你指纹
The police took your fingerprints
我不想听
l won't listen to this
不由你不听！
Yes, you will!
你叫宝丽安！
You're Polly Ann Costello!
父亲杀死母亲后自杀！
Your father killed your mother, then killed himself!
你被收养，一九九零年出走
You ran away from a foster home in Oakland in 1990!
案底：科州责淫…  别说！
Arrests: Denver, soliciting... Stop it!
加州、怀州卖淫！读下去好吗？
San Jose, Cheyenne, soliciting! Shall l read the rest?
藏可卡因、持械行凶
Possession of crack cocaine! Assault with a deadly weapon!
为什么不继续当娼？
Tell me something. Why did you stop hooking?
你反正已确定人生路向
You had your future pretty well mapped out
我不得已
l did what l had to do
就像你对付姬丝桃？
Just like you did with Cristal
我不是娼妓
l'm not a whore
你不是
No...you're not
你会成为红星
You're going to be a big star
街上挂着你的大型海报
Your face will be up on billboards
你会替星尘赚大钱
And you will make a lot of money for the Stardust
你放过安德鲁？
You'd let him get away with this?
他今年在天堂酒店演唱
Andrew Carver is at the Paradiso this year
明年或在星尘
He might be at the Stardust next year
他是自己人，你也是
He's part of the team. So are you
慕莉呢？
What about Molly?
他会赔钱，慕莉可开时装店
l'll see he gives her enough money to have a dress shop
告诉我
Tell me something
你收费多少？
What did you charge?
卖淫的收费
Hooking
五十元，有时一百元
Fifty. A hundred sometimes
自贬身价，你的功夫着实一流
You got low self-esteem, baby. You're a fantastic fuck
我在赞赏你啊
l was paying you a compliment
够钟演出
Showtime
安德鲁，麻烦你
Andrew Carver, please
打扮得好
Hello, baby. Looking good
他在等候你
He's ready for you
你来得快
lt didn't take you long
我喜欢你无上装
l like you better topless
等一等我无下装
Wait till you see me bottomless
我正在等
l'm waiting
统统脱掉
Take the rest off
得
Sure
你出声，我捅死你！
You make a sound, l'll fucking kill you!
好
Okay, okay
贱种！
Fucker! Fuck off!
别打扰，他想睡觉
He says he wants to sleep
筋疲力竭
Tired him out, huh?
药物关系，她仍未清醒
She's still out. lt's the medication
她平安吗？
ls she okay?
平安
She's okay
慕莉
Molly?
我刚去找过安德鲁…
l just went to Carver...
把他踢得不似人形
and kicked the shit out of him
我爱你
l love you
请问姬丝桃在哪？  319号房
Cristal Connors, please. Room 319
记得我的金石良言吗？
You know the best advice l ever gave you?
最后剩下你的话…
lf you're the only one left standing...
那空缺非你莫属
they'll hire you
谢谢来宾，晚安
Thank you and good night, ladies and gentlemen
到此为止
Cristal has left the building
对不起，姬丝桃
l'm sorry, Cristal
我明白你多内疚
Yeah. l know just how sorry you are
我当上主角，也使同一手段
How do you think l got my first lead?
总会有人更年轻、更野心…
There's always someone younger and hungrier...
跟着你下楼梯
coming down the stairs after you
为什么不说我推你？
Why didn't you tell anyone?
亲爱的…我需要歇一歇
Oh, hell, darling...l needed a rest
况且，我也获得一大笔赔款
Besides, my lawyers got me a real nice settlement
我要走了
l have to go
不给我来个热吻？
Aren't you going to give me a big kiss?
再见，亲爱的
Bye, darling
上车！快点！
Come on! Hurry up!
上来吧，今天算你走运
Hop in, pard This here is your lucky day
出发
Let's go
有博一博吗？
So did you gamble?
赢？
Did you win?
赢了什么？
What did you win?
赢回自己
Me
妈的
Oh, fuck
是你
lt's you
还我的行李箱来！贱种！
l want my fucking suitcase, asshole!
我正在驾驶啊！离谱！
l'm driving! Jesus fucking Christ!
留意交通！
Watch the fucking road!
还你行李箱好了
Be cool! l'll get your suitcase.
误会而已，别冲动
lt was a mistake. Mellow out!
女神娜美
NOMl MALONE lS GODDESS